http://www.freshpair.com/pages/privacy-and-security

Quickshop
+
How to Fit
Need a little more assistance?
Privacy | Security | Freshpair
Freshpair.com respects your privacy. We do not rent or sell your personal information to anyone! We use the information we collect strictly to improve the quality of your shopping experience and we never rent, trade, or sell your private information to others. We also use the highest encryption standards available through an SSL certification.
Privacy Policy
Freshpair's Privacy Policy provides you with the information and policies regarding our information collection processes, how we use the information we collect, and our privacy protection assurance. By using the Freshpair site, you agree to the conditions of this privacy policy.
The information we collect
How we use and share the personal information we collect
Communications from Freshpair
Changes to Privacy Policy
Questions or comments
The information we collect
Each time a user visits Freshpair, certain information is collected. That information below is specific to your visit and whether you browse, shop or register. Depending on those actions, different unique information is gathered. The information below details the types of information we collect, how it is gathered and what is done with it.
IP address, cookies, pixel tags, and gifs: non-identifying information
Part of each visit to Freshpair is registered through an IP address that may help us diagnose issues with our servers and correct errors. Your IP address also allows us to gather broad, non-personal demographics that help us to analyze traffic patterns and how our site is browsed.
Cookies allow you to use the shopping cart on our site. Without cookies one cannot order from Freshpair online. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers transferred from our site to your computer so that we may identify you when you visit. These files also provide non-personally identifiable browsing and purchasing information which Freshpair and its third-party vendors use to serve you more efficiently.
Most computers are pre-set to accept cookies. You can opt to have your computer warn you each time cookies are being selected or you can opt to deny cookies. If you refuse the acceptance of cookies on your computer, you will not be able to complete an online order with us.
In order to monitor the success and usage of our email marketing campaigns, Freshpair may implement 'message format' or 'message open' sensing technology. These technologies require pixel tags or clear Gifs which are unseen to the user, but send the appropriate information to our tracking system. This information allows us to identify if your email accepts HTML or text only emails so that we may send you the appropriate format.
Registration and order information
Freshpair uses a registration process and order form so that you can purchase online, request information and receive service from us. Your personal contact information (i.e. name, email address, telephone number, mailing address, etc.) is used to send you your order and to fulfill marketing programs.
Credit card information is completely secure and protected and collected for the sole purpose of billing you for your purchase.
Users may browse our products and information without registering. Registration is optional and only required to shop online.
How we use and share the information we collect
Freshpair is proud to inform you that we do not sell or share your personal information or email. Your information is only used to complete your order and for marketing purposes, if you have opted for this feature.
Should you select the optional opportunity to receive emails from us about current offers and incentives, we will also use your email for this purpose. If you have not selected this option, you will not receive promotional emails.
If you have opted to receive promotional email, you may choose to remove this feature from your account at any time and the emails will be stopped.
Your contact information may also be used should we ever need to contact you regarding your order.
Gift certificates and gifts also require that certain information is sent to third parties. This information receives the same courtesy detailed above for our customers.
Communications from Freshpair
Freshpair offers many modes of communication to our customers. Freshpair also reserves the right to communicate with our registered users regarding their order should the need arise.
Communication regarding transaction and account maintenance
Freshpair communications include order confirmations, order updates, problems with orders, delivery issues (as needed), and management of accounts (should issues arise).
HTML emails and marketing
Freshpair offers our users an email option that allows us to communicate with you regarding sales, incentives, new products, and other offers. If you receive these emails, you may opt at any time to remove yourself from this mailing list. If you do not receive emails, you may add yourself to this feature in your account management area.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Changes to Privacy Policy
Freshpair's privacy policy was last updated on May 29, 2018. Freshpair reserves the right to amend or append this policy at any time by posting those revisions on your site. Any changes will only affect information collected after this post date unless otherwise stated.
Questions or comments
Freshpair invites you to communicate with us should you have a question or would like to voice a concern regarding our privacy or security policies. Please email us at customercare@freshpair.com and a customer service associate will respond to you in a timely manner. You may also call us at (347) 472-1242.
Back To Top
